(鬼鮫)ようやく
おとなしくなりましたか。
You've finally settled down.
フゥ… まったく 手こずらせる。
Sheesh, what a handful.
(イタチ)戻ったか。
ええ➡
You're back.
Yeah, but having to bring him back
without killing him,
殺さずに生け捕るってのが
面倒でしたがね。
was quite a bother.
少し 降ってきましたね。
It's starting to rain.
荒れそうだな。
Looks like it'll storm.
木陰で 雨をしのぎましょう。
Let's take cover under a tree,
体が冷えますよ。
or we'll catch a cold.
リーダーが 連絡を待っている。
Leader is waiting for word that
we've captured him.
我々の捕獲が完了し次第➡
Immediately thereafter,
三尾と四尾を 同時に
封印する手はずだからな。
the sealing of the Three-Tails
and Four-Tails is to occur simultaneously.
少しくらい 待たせておけば
いいんですよ。
So we make him wait a little.
封印を始めたら どうせ➡
Once the sealing begins,
we'll be working for quite some time.
しばらくは
働き詰めなんですから。
死にそうだな。
年寄りは ていねいに扱え。
He seems near death.
You must handle the elderly
with care.
コイツを知らないから
そんなこと言うんですよ。
You say that because
you don't know him.
四尾の熔遁を使う この人柱力は➡
This Jinchuriki who uses the
Corrosion Style Jutsu of the Four-Tails
そんなタマじゃないですよ。
isn't what you think.
直接 戦っていないあなたには➡
You didn't fight him yourself,
私の苦労は
わからないでしょうがね。
so you wouldn't understand
what I went through.
(イタチ)フン…。
まぁ 一人で行かせてくれと
言ったのは 私ですがね。
But, I was the one who asked
to go alone.
なんなら あなたのノルマも➡
Say, want me to beat
your assignment half-dead too?
私が 半殺しに
しちゃいましょうか？
そう はしゃぐな 鬼鮫。
Don't get so excited, Kisame.
少し 疲れていましてね➡
Well, I'm a bit tired, you see.
早く すべての尾獣を
狩ってしまいたいものです。
I wish we could catch all
the Tailed Beasts already.
そう 焦ることもないさ。
Don't be so impatient...
It's going to take some time.
まだ 時間はかかるだろうからな。
それは どうでしょうかね。
I wonder about that.
There's just a few more, right?
残りは あとわずかでしょ。
九尾は 最後に 封印しなければ
ならないと 決められている。
And it's been decided that
the Nine-Tails will be sealed last...
でなければ バランスが崩れ
封印像が砕け散ると➡
Otherwise, the balance
will be disrupted,
and the sealing statue
will be pulverized...
そう リーダーは言っていましたが…。
That's what Leader said...
どうせ 人柱力は
生け捕りですからね。
After all, the Jinchuriki need
to be captured alive.
さっさと狩って拘束しておけば
いいだけの話じゃないですか？
So I say just catch them quickly
and leave them tied up.
フッ… 別に それでも構わんが➡
Humph... Fine with me,
but remember that Deidara failed.
デイダラも失敗したしな。
最後に封印するなら
最後に狩っても 同じことだ。
If he's going to be sealed last,
it's no big deal if
we capture him last.
それに 今となっては
暁も目立ちすぎた。
And besides, Akatsuki is becoming
too conspicuous lately.
早くに
九尾の人柱力を拘束すれば➡
If we capture the Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki
too soon,
木ノ葉隠れが 今以上に
ざわめき立つ。
the Hidden Leaf will become
even more of a nuisance.
ヘッ そうですかね。
Heh... You really think so?
木ノ葉隠れという里は➡
The Hidden Leaf Village has
very strong links with other villages.
特に 他里とのパイプが強い。
連携されたら 我々の行動も
しづらくなる。
If they begin to collaborate,
it will be difficult for us to act.
今は 八尾までを 目立たず
速やかに回収するほうが賢い。
It will be wiser to collect up
to the Eight-Tails
with as little commotion as possible.
なるほど。 そう言われれば
そうですかね。
I see. I guess you're right.
There's the summons.
呼び出しか…。
サボリが バレましたかね。
We've been caught dawdling.
(ペイン)遅いぞ。
You're late...
(鬼鮫)ちょうど 人柱力を
狩り終えたところでしてね➡
We had just finished catching
the Jinchuruki when you contacted us.
逃げないように 縛り上げてて
遅くなったんですよ。
We tied him up good to
make sure he didn't escape.
That's what took us longer.
それで 用件は何です？
So, what's up?
(ペイン)早急に 伝えておきたい
情報があってな。
I got an urgent message
I wanted to relay to you.
大蛇丸が 殺された。
Orochimaru has been killed.
(鬼鮫)フフッ 暁を抜けて10年➡
It's been ten years since
he deserted us...
殺す手間が省けた
というところですか。
So we've been spared the trouble
of killing him ourselves.
ヤツの死にざま あのゾンビコンビの
死にざまくらい➡
I would've loved to see him die
as much as I would've loved to
see the Zombie Combo die.
見たかったですね。
(ペイン)飛段と角都は仲間だ。
そういう言い方はよせ。
Hidan and Kakuzu were
our comrades.
Don't say such things.
失礼。 確かあのとき
飛段たちをやったのは…。
Sorry... Back then,
they were done in by...
(ゼツ)木ノ葉の連中だったな。
The Hidden Leaf.
カカシと九尾の人柱力の小隊だよ。
The squad with Kakashi and
the Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki.
(トビ)強いですよね あの小隊。
They're strong, that team.
Even Deidara got his butt kicked.
デイダラさんも ボコボコにされるわけだ。
トビッ。 テメエ それ以上言ってみろ。
Tobi!
Say one more word and my patience
will run out! It will!
オイラの堪忍袋が爆発するぜ。
アハハッ。 まぁまぁ 堪忍袋って
ガマンするための袋であって➡
It takes self-control to be patient...
デイダラさんのは 爆発袋でしょ。
すぐにキレんだから。
And your fuse is too short for that.
テメエ トビッ！ コラーッ！
Why you--! Tobi! You!
デイダラ 静かにしろ。
それじゃ トビの言うとおりだ。
Pipe down, Deidara. Tobi's right.
チッ。
アハハッ 先輩怒られた。
You got chewed out!
(ペイン)それからトビ。
お前は いつもひと言多い。
But Tobi, you always talk too much.
Respect your superiors.
先輩は立てろ。
は～い すみませ～ん。
Okay! Sorry!
こんなんで 残りの人柱力を
集めきれますかね。
And we're supposed to get
the remaining Jinchuriki with these two?
ハァ。
しかし あの大蛇丸を倒すとは
たいした手だれですね。
But killing Orochimaru took
special skill. Who did it?
誰がやったんです？
うちはサスケだ。
Uchiha Sasuke.
大蛇丸は オイラがぶっ倒すと
決めてたのによ… うん。
I was gonna be the one to
bring Orochimaru down.
フッ やりますね。
さすが イタチさんの弟だ。
Hmm... He's good.
I'd expect nothing less from
your kid brother, Itachi-san.
今 仲間を集め回ってる。
それも厄介な忍ばかりだ。
He's gathering members...
Really troublesome ninja at that.
と いうと？
お前もよく知っているだろう。
What do you mean?
You know them well too...
霧隠れの鬼灯兄弟。
あれの片割れだ。
One of the Hozuki Brothers
of the Hidden Mist...
水月か。 懐かしいですね。
You mean, Suigetsu?
That brings back memories.
それに 天秤の重吾もいる。
せいぜい気をつけろ。
And also, Bipolar Jugo.
So be on your guard,
Itachi and Kisame...
イタチ 鬼鮫。 おそらく
お前たちを狙っている。
I dare say they're targeting you two.
他の者も一応 うちはサスケのことは
頭に入れておけ。
And the rest of you should keep
Uchiha Sasuke in mind.
イタチや鬼鮫の情報を得ようと
暁を標的にするかもしれん。
After getting information
about Itachi and Kisame,
they may just come after Akatsuki.
鬼鮫 どんなヤツなんだ？
その水月ってのは うん？
Kisame, what kind of guy is he...?
This Suigetsu... hmm?
10年も前だ。
かわいい顔で笑う子でしてね。
It happened ten years ago...
He had such a cute smile.
鬼人 再不斬の再来と呼ばれた
神童ですよ。
A child prodigy who's been called
the reincarnation of
the demonic Zabuza.
(香燐)テメエ 陸に上がった河童か！
Are you a river child
who got stranded on land?!
いちいち水分補給で
座り込んでんじゃねえよ！
Quit stopping to drink water so often!
へぇ ソイツはいろいろ
おもしろそうだな。
Hmm... They seem like an interesting lot.
ちょっとちょっと 変な興味
持たないでくださいよ。
Hey, don't get too interested.
And just leave me out of it!
巻き込まれるのはごめんですから。
そんなことより イタチ 鬼鮫。
四尾を急いで連れてこい。
Never mind that already.
Itachi, Kisame...
hurry up and
get the Four-Tails.
三尾と一緒に封印するぞ。
わかった。
We'll seal him at the same time
as the Three-Tails!
Understood.
やれやれ。
少しは休めると思ったんですがね。
Cripes, and I thought
we'd get to rest a bit.
仕方あるまい。 急ぐぞ。
We have no choice. Let's hurry.
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
The Ones Moving Out
(綱手)サスケに会うために
最も確率の高い➡
We target the member of Akatsuki
with whom we have
the highest chance of meeting Sasuke.
暁のメンバーを狙うか。
まあ 筋は通っているが。
Well, I can see the logic in that.
(綱手)
うちはイタチ さて どうしたものか。
Uchiha Itachi... What shall we do?
(サクラ)暁の身柄を
一人でも拘束してしまえば➡
If we're able to take just one of
the Akatsuki into custody,
あとは イビキさんが
イタチについての情報を➡
Ibiki can get information about
Itachi out of him.
聞き出してくれると
思うんですけど。
確かに 各小隊には可能であれば
暁の身柄を拘束し➡
I've already issued an order to
all teams to capture
a member of Akatsuki
if the opportunity presents itself,
連行するようにと命じてはいるが。
and to transport him here.
(カカシ)実際は難しいでしょうね。
That will probably be very difficult.
カカシ先生。
(カカシ)ヤツらは そう簡単に
口を割るような連中じゃないし➡
Kakashi-sensei...
We won't be able to make them
talk so easily.
今までやり合った連中の
能力を見れば➡
Even those we've already encountered
were far too dangerous
危なすぎて とてもじゃないが
拘束なんて考えられなかった。
and we couldn't even think about
taking them into custody.
(ナルト)
そんじゃ どうするんだってばよ。
Then what're we gonna do?!
ま イタチと当たるまで➡
Well, until we come across Itachi,
根気よく捜すしか
ないんじゃない？
I don't think we have any choice
but to be very patient and search.
もう限界…。
ちょっと休憩しようよ。
I can't go on.
Let's take a short break...
お前がチンタラ歩いてるかぎり
いつまでたっても着かねえよ！
As long as you drag your feet like that,
we'll never get there!
(水月)悪かったね。
ボクはキミと違って繊細なんだ。
Well, pardon me.
But unlike you,
I have a very delicate constitution.
はぁ？ つうかもう
そのまま蒸発しちまえ 水オバケ！
Huh? Look, just evaporate,
you water ghost!
フン… キミこそ消えたらどうなの？
他に行くとこあったんだろ。
Why don't you get lost instead?
I thought you had somewhere else to go?
クッ…。
(サスケ)着いたぞ。
We're here.
(鬼鮫)こりゃ 大物ですね。
This is a big one.
(ペイン)来たか…。
So you've come...
では これより
三尾から順に封印にかかる。
All right, we'll begin the sealing
starting with the Three-Tails.
よし… 集合しろ！
All right! Assemble.
始めるぞ。
Let's begin.
ここだ。
いかにも怪しげって感じだよね。
We're here.
What a creepy-looking place.
行くぞ。
Let's go.
へぇ… こんな廃墟に
アジトがあったなんてね。 初耳だよ。
A hideout in an old ruin like this...
大蛇丸は関係ない。
It's news to me.
Orochimaru has nothing to do with this.
オレの一族が使っていた武器屋だ。
ここで戦いの準備をととのえる。
My clan used this as a weapons store.
We'll prepare for the battle
that will be fought here.
ふ～ん。
同じような通路が続くから
迷うね ここ。
The passageways look so similar,
it's easy to get lost in here.
しかし辛気臭い所だな。
息が詰まるぜ。
But what a depressing place.
It stifles my breath.
(デンカ)辛気臭い所で悪かったな。
Sorry if it's depressing here.
ん？
久しぶりだな デンカにヒナ。
Huh?
It's been a long time,
Denka and Hina.
(デンカ)やっぱり サスケのボウヤか。
It's young Sasuke, after all...
(ヒナ)ここに何の用だフニャ？
What's your business here?
ここに何の用だフニャ？
武器に薬 その他もろもろだ。
Weapons and medicine...
and various other things.
これからの戦闘に備える。
これって…。
ヘヘッ しゃべるタヌキですか。
We're preparing for battle.
This is...
ほら こっちおいで… うわっ！
Oh, a talking raccoon dog?
Hey, come over here.
コイツらは忍猫だ。
Yikes...
うかつに手を出すな。
ズタズタにされるぞ。
They're ninja cats.
Don't approach them carelessly.
そういうことは
もっと早く言ってほしいな。
They'll tear you apart.
You should warn us about stuff
like that from the beginning.
手土産は持ってきたフニャ？
ほら… またたびボトルだ。
Did you bring us a present?
Here... a bottle of catnip.
毎度フニャ。
ついてきな。 猫バアに会わせる。
Thank you.
Follow me. I'll take you to Granny Cat.
恩に着るよ 猫バア。
(猫バア)久しぶりだってのに
ずいぶん慌ただしいね。
I owe you, Granny Cat.
It's been so long since we've met,
but you're in such a hurry.
あぁ 大事な用がある。
Yeah. I have something important to do.
お前は忍猫じゃないよな？
よしよし。
You're not a ninja cat, right?
There, there.
あぁ ダメ。 これでも小さいか。
すまん。
No, stop. Even this one is too small.
Sorry.
やっぱり
イタチの所に行くんかいな？
So you're going to see Itachi,
after all?
アンタら２人は
小さい頃からよく知ってるが➡
I've known you both since
you were little,
まさか
こんなことになろうとはね…。
but little did I imagine
it would come to this...
今や うちはもお前たち２人だけ。
それが殺し合わにゃならんとは。
You two are all that's left
of the Uchiha Clan...
And now, you'll have to
fight to the death.
もう行く。 今まで世話になった。
I'm going. Thanks for everything.
ねぇ バアちゃん この人に合う
もっと大きい服ない？
Granny, don't we have something bigger
for him to wear?
その箱にあるだろう！
(タマキ)それが 全然ダメなのよ。
In that box over there!
だったら
そこのカーテンでも巻いときな！
Nothing fits.
Then just wrap that curtain
around him!
ったく！
うちは服屋じゃないんだよ！
I don't run a clothing store!
バアちゃん…
お金もらってるのに失礼でしょ！
Granny! What a rude thing to say,
considering he paid us!
(重吾)うん！
(自来也)
サスケと会うためにイタチを追うか…。
Fine.
Pursue Itachi in order to meet up
with Sasuke, eh?
だが イタチを捜し当てたところで
どうする？
Well then...
Say we find Itachi. What next?
それについてですが…
ちょっと オレに考えがあります。
About that...
少し時間をいただけませんか？
I have an idea.
Can you spare some time?
なんだ 冴えん顔だのぉ。
エロ仙人…
何しに来たんだってばよぉ。
You don't look too pleased.
Pervy Sage?
What're you doing here?
久しぶりに会った弟子と
メシでも どうかと思ってのぉ。
I hadn't seen my apprentice in a while,
so I thought maybe
we could share a meal.
それって… おごり？
まったく カカシ先生ってば…。
こっちは すぐにでも➡
Are you treating?
"Ichiraku Ramen"
Cripes, what's with Kakashi-sensei?
動き出さなきゃなんねえ
ってのによぉ。
Here, we're ready to move out
any time.
しかたなかろう。 出発とは
相応の準備がいる。
準備？
It can't be helped.
There are lots of things to prepare for.
お前ら 一小隊だけじゃ
どうにもならんだろうからのぉ。
Prepare for what?
One small squad isn't enough.
それってば どういうこと？
いいか？ イタチを倒せば
サスケの目的は消える。
What do you mean by that?
Listen. If Itachi is defeated,
つまり イタチは拘束するしかない
ということだ。
Sasuke will lose his purpose
in coming.
So we have no choice
but to find a way to detain Itachi.
そのためには もっと大人数で
隊を組み 動く必要がある。
And that will require a coordinated effort
with more ninja.
今ごろカカシは
その作業に追われてるはずだ。
Right now, Kakashi has his hands full
trying to get this organized.
そういうことか。
Is that how it is?
う～ん しかし
相手が相手だからのぉ。
この任務 一筋縄ではいくまい。
But we're dealing with Itachi here.
Ordinary methods won't work.
そうだろうな。 でも どうしても
避けて通れねえんだ。
Probably not...
サスケを連れ戻すために か…。
わかってると思うが➡
And we can't just avoid him, can we?
And just bring Sasuke back?
今やサスケは大蛇丸をやるほどの力を
身につけておる。
I'm sure you understand,
but Sasuke has grown powerful enough
to kill Orochimaru.
んなことは わかってる！
けど 昔 サクラちゃんとも
約束しちまったしな。
I know that...
But I made a promise
to Sakura long ago...
サスケは必ず連れ帰るって。
That I'd "bring Sasuke back without fail".
まっすぐ 自分の言葉は曲げねえ！
And I can't go back on my word.
((自来也 : 忍の才能で
いちばん大切なのは➡
What is most important to a ninja
(持ってる術の数なんかじゃあねえ。
大切なのは あきらめねえ…))
is not the number of jutsu
he possesses...
What's important is...
ド根性だ！
- To never give up!
それが オレの忍道だからよ。
Determination!
That's my Ninja Way!
フン 相変わらずのバカだのぉ。
しかたねえだろ
エロ仙人の弟子なんだから！ チッ。
You're as foolish as ever.
I can't help it.
After all, I'm the apprentice
of the Pervy Sage.
ったく… ワシも出来の悪い弟子を
持ったもんだのぉ。
Geez, what a rude apprentice
I'm stuck with.
出来が悪いって
どういう意味だってばよぉ！
"Rude"?! What does that mean?
そのまんまの意味に
決まっとろうが このバカ弟子め！
Exactly that, you rude apprentice.
そういうエロ仙人だって➡
ダメダメじゃんの
エロエロじじいじゃねえかよ！
You're one to talk, Pervy Sage!
You're a no-good, perverted old man!
ほら これも食っとけ。
Here, eat this too.
Oh...
やっぱ 一楽のチャーシューは最高だな。
Ichiraku's roast pork is still the best.
(トビ)ホント 尾獣の封印って
しんどいっすよね。
Cripes, sealing the Tailed Beast
is such a pain!
こんなのが
あと何回かあるんでしょう？
考えただけで うんざり！
And there's more to go after this, right?
(デイダラ)さて
どっちへ行くかな？ うん。
Just thinking about it frazzles me.
Now then... which way? Hmm...
(トビ)あぁ ちょっと先輩
あの 「どっちへ行くかな？」って➡
Umm... Excuse me, Senpai,
"which way" what?
どっちと どっちのことを
言ってんすか？
そんなん決まってんだろ！
What do you mean?
カカシ率いる 九尾の人柱力。
それか うちはサスケかだ。
What do you think?!
Do we go for the Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki
whose team is led by Kakashi...
or Uchiha Sasuke...?
え～ いや もう
どっちも やめましょうよ。
Hey, we shouldn't mess with either one!
だいたい ボクらのノルマは
終わってるし…。
そもそも サスケは
尾獣でもなんでもないし～。
Our assignment is over!
And furthermore,
Sasuke's not even a Tailed Beast!
冗談じゃねえ！
九尾の人柱力には
殴られた借りがある。
Are you kidding...?!
The Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki owes me one
for punching me.
カカシには 右腕やられたしな うん。
And Kakashi got my right arm...
それに オイラが殺すはずだった
大蛇丸をやりやがった➡
Then there's Uchiha Sasuke...
うちはサスケも許さねえ。
I can't forgive him 'cuz he killed
Orochimaru, whom I planned to kill.
あぁ もう この人ったら➡
Geez...
言い出したら
ホント 聞かないんだから。
Once he sets his mind to something,
he just won't listen.
なんか言ったか？
いいえ。
Did you say something?
フン… いくぞ トビ！
No.
Humph. We're going, Tobi.
やれやれ デイダラのヤツ
すぐにでも 我々のノルマか➡
Oh dear... That Deidara has gotten
all worked up
弟さんのところに
向かいそうな勢いでしたが➡
about going after your little brother.
いいんですか？ イタチさん。
Is that okay with you, Itachi-san?
いくぞ。
Let's go!
なるほど 考えたな。
I see. You've given it
quite a bit of thought.
あのさ もっと
大人数じゃなくていいのかよ。
Say, shouldn't we have even more guys?
単に数がいれば
いいってもんじゃないよ。
今回の場合
二小隊１チームが望ましいね。
It's not simply a matter of manpower.
For this job, I think two squads
working together are ideal.
拘束すべき対象が少人数
つまり１人から２人の場合➡
If our targets are few in number,
namely one or two,
こちらが 三小隊以上になると
相手に見つかりやすいし➡
having more than three squads
will make us too easy to detect
命令系統が混乱し
逆に機動力が低下するからね。
as well as interfere with
the chain of command.
And it will end up hindering our mobility.
拘束は 殺すより
はるかに テクニックがいるからのぉ。
Restraining the enemy requires
much more technique than mere killing.
隊の連携を考えれば➡
任務をこれまで
ある程度ともにしてきた者を➡
In coordinating the squads,
it would be wise to choose members
選抜したほうがよいのぉ。
who are accustomed to working together.
ま 現時点では ベストの編成だろう。
Well, right now,
this is the best plan.
おそれいります。
しかし 出発だってのに
イヤな天気だなぁ どうも。
Thank you.
Well, we're about ready to set out,
but I don't like this weather.
よっしゃ～！ 行くってばよ！
(キバ)熱くなりすぎてるヤツには
ちょうどいい雨じゃないっすか。
All right! Let's go!
The rain is perfect for cooling off someone
so fired up.
では これより うちはイタチの探索
および 拘束任務を命ずる！
Okay, I'm issuing the order
for a mission
皆 細心の注意を払って
ことにあたれ！
to locate and detain Uchiha Itachi!
All of you, be extremely careful
and carry out your duties!
(ナルトたち)オッス！
- Right!
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
life always throws you curveballs and the reason of that is
yo kono yo wa hitosujinawa de ikanai sore wa naze nara
it's a test made by God so that's why it's quite hard
kamisama ga tsukutta tesuto dakara muzukashii nda
arts? science? or rather how about ethics?
bunkei rikei mushiro doutoku kimi nara kore wo dou toku
this is just like life so put your heart and soul into seriousness
kore wa maru de jinsei dakara uchikomu shinken ni
we worry ourselves lose ourselves and we keep asking ourselves questions
bokura wa nayamu mayou nandomo jibun ni toikakeru
we aren't one and relentesly persue our search for answers
hitotsu ja nai kotae sagashi gamushara ni oikakeru
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
the current me would tell me that if I was from the future
mirai no bokura nara ima no boku ni oshiete agerareru
you should keep pursuing it until your efforts change yourself
kimi no doryoku ga jishin ni kawaru toki made oitsuzukereba ii
Next Episode
Basically, this search team is organized
by one ninja and two ninja hounds.
However, Yamato and Hinata
the Visual Jutsu User
will accompany Naruto just in case he,
a Jinchuriki, is attacked.
I'm counting on you, Hinata.
Yes.
Listen, we're after Itachi and Sasuke.
But, even if you find either of them,
come back to this point.
Now, go!
The Hunt
Next time: "The Hunt"
- Good night!
That was a tough recording session.
Sakura, how about stopping for
some ramen on the way home--?
No thanks.
That was a quick answer.
N-Naruto-kun...
What's wrong, Hinata?
I-If it's okay, I...
I...?
- I-I mean...
- "I mean" what?!
Come to think of it, lately Hinata's only line
has been "Naruto-kun".
That's true!
Starting from the next episode,
maybe we can keep using
the same line over and over again.
(ヒカル)自分たちは
ある任務の遂行のため➡
What?!
That's what the director said.
Even though it's the same line,
この島に舞い降りたっす。
I'm saying it from
the bottom of my heart.
So when you're embarrassed?
そう それは
伝説の黒魔導士 ゼレフの捕縛。
N-Naruto-kun...
When you're happy!
Naruto-kun...
When you're angry!
もう一つは… 忘れたっす。
N-Naruto-kun!
- Cry!
- N-Naruto...
いや その…
自分 なんで 一人なんすか？
- Flustered!
- Naruto-kun!
- Smile!
- Naruto-kun...
みんなは どこへ… う うぇ～！
Scream!
Naruto-kun!
That's okay.
We'll be using these lines for a while.
Huh?!
"Studio"
N-No way.